# DAVE WOLFBERG

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full Stack Software Developer with experience building a diverse set of frontend and backend projects. Lifelong learner with a growth mindset who is excited to contribute to impactful projects. Patient puzzle solver with the ability to stay calm and collected in high pressure situations and drive to deliver the highest quality work under stringent time restrictions. Charismatic communicator and highly collaborative professional who has spent a decade on the road as a touring musician developing grit, flexibility, and a strong team ethic.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Software Engineer, 07/2022 - 10/2022

## SPJ Solutions, Sacramento, CA

- Designed and Implemented REST API endpoints that streamlined virtual application migrations from NSX-V to NSX-T networks.
- Implemented frontend installation wizards that guided users through processes such as virtual data center creation, AVI controller deployment, application migrations, and file imports/ exports.
- Utilized VMware's AVI controller API to create deployable vCenter Cloud environment via SPJ's cITopus App.

## Freelance Software Developer, 03/2022 - 07/2022 Self-Employed, Remote, CA

- Facilitated clients visions for Wordpress sites allowing them to edit their own custom websites.
- Installed cyber security protocols to protect Wordpress domains from cyber attacks.
- Created custom themes using PHP based on the needs of the businesses.

## Software Engineering Fellow, 12/2021 - 03/2022 General Assembly, Remote

- Created interactive touchscreen Pedalboard Builder App for musicians with MERN stack, AWS S3, and React-Beautiful Drag-n-Drop.
- Built "Make-Your-Own-Burger-App" using Express, and MongoDB that allows user to create burgers and view their creations.
- Collaborated with team of 2 others to make "Smart Cocktail Recommendation App" utilizing Django, Python, PostgreSQL, and Materialize.
- Learned essential fundamental skills in web development, computer science and database engineering principles.

## Guitarist - Touring/Session Musician , 05/2013 - 11/2021 Warner Media, And Various Artists

- Worked on tours, recordings and film orchestrations.
- Provided musical background for live shows such as ballets, operas, musical theatre and cabarets.
- Managed projects with dance departments creating scores and choreography.



Los Angeles, CA 90068



(201) 615-4663



Dave.M.Wolfberg@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS, TypeScript, JavaScript, Python, Ruby, PHP, SQL.
- API design and implementation.
- React, Express, Node, Django, Ruby on Rails, Wordpress.
- Bootstrap, Materialize.
- PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Sequelize, Postico.
- Winston Logger.
- Docker, Mocha, AWS.
- Trello, Lucid Chart, Creating ERDs, Wireframes, and Pitch decks.
- Zoom, Slack, Jira, Zoho, Github.
- Expansive knowledge of music, art and social media trends.

## WEBSITE, PORTFOLIO, PROFILES

- https://github.com/Wolfcodes91/
- http://portfolio-davewolfberg.herokuapp.com/
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/davewolfberg/

## CERTIFICATIONS

Mimo - Certificate of Achievement in Python (May '22)

Mimo - Certificate of Achievement in SQL (May '22)

Mimo - Certificate of Achievement in Frontend Development (May '22)

#### **EDUCATION**

Certificate, Software Engineering Immersive , 03/2022

**General Assembly - Remote** 

Bachelor of Arts, Composition And Performance, 05/2013 Berklee College of Music - Boston, MA